Here I am with Visual Studio Code.
这里我使用 Visual Studio 代码
I've just opened the editor.
我刚打开了编辑
I'm going to create a new file.
我要创建一个新的文件
The first thing I'm going to do is save it.
我要做的第一件事就是拯救它
I'll save it in my temp directory.
我会把它保存在临时目录里
We'll call it hello.cpp.
我们会叫它 hello.cpp
I will write include iostream and create a main function.
我将写包括 iostream  并创建一个 main 函数
I'll say std cout ''Hello world''. Then I'll save that.
我会说 " 你好世界 " 那我就省了吧
The next thing I'll do is I will open up a terminal down here.
接下来我要做的就是在这里打开一个终端
I'll go to my temp directory.
我去我的 temp 目录
I've already installed g++.
我已经安装了 + +
So if I check, I have g++.
所以如果我检查一下 我有 g++
So I can write g++ hello.cpp.
所以我可以写 g++ hello.cpp
That should give me an a.out file.
那应该给我一个 a.out 文件
It does and it prints "Hello World". All set.
它确实印上了 " Hello World "   一切都好了